Rochester, New York and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO Memorabilia 6239 MB
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Rochester, New York and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO Memorabilia
1986- 2007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Garlock, Jonathan
Anderson, Marilyn
Rochester and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO
6239 MB
7.11 cubic feet
7.1 linear ft.
Memorabilia.
8233173
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 19, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 04, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Garlock, Jonathan; Anderson, Marilyn; Rochester and Vicinity Labor Council
8233173
- Labor Film Series Flyers (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 2000 - Lyceum (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 2001 Lyceum (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 2002 Lyceum (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 2003 Lyceum (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 2004 Lyceum (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 2005 Lyceum (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 2006 Lyceum (Box 1, Folder 8)
- 2007 Lyceum (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Labor Day Parade Flyers (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Marshal T-shirt -- Labor Day '99, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Marshal T-shirt -- Labor Day '98, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Marshal T-shirt -- Labor Day '97, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Marshal T-shirt -- Labor Day '96, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- T-shirt -- Labor Day '95, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Marshal T-shirt -- Labor Day '94, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Marshal T-shirt -- Labor Day '93, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Marshal T-shirt -- Labor Day '92, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Marshal T-shirt -- Labor Day 2007 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Marshal T-shirt -- Labor Day 2006 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Marshal T-shirt -- Labor Day 2005 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Marshal T-shirt -- Labor Day 2004 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Marshal T-shirt -- Labor Day 2003 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Marshal T-shirt -- Labor Day 2002 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Marshal T-shirt -- Labor Day 2001 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Marshal T-shirt -- Labor Day 2000 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Broadsides (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Calendars (Box 1, Folder 28)
- T-shirt -- Labor Day 2007 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- T-shirt -- Labor Day 2005 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- T-shirt -- Labor Day 2004 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- T-shirt -- Labor Day 2002 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- T-shirt -- Labor Day 2001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- T-shirt -- Labor Day 2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- T-shirt -- Labor Day '99, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- T-shirt -- Labor Day '98, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- T-shirt -- Labor Day '97, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- T-shirt -- Labor Day '95, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Rochester Labor Film Series - T-Shirt, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Rochester Labor Film Series - T-Shirt, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Rochester Labor Film Series - T-Shirt, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Rochester Labor Film Series - 1996 - T-Shirt (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Rochester Labor Film Series - 1993 - T-Shirt (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Rochester Labor Film Series - '99 -- Sweatshirt, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Rochester Labor Film Series - '98 - T-Shirt, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Rochester Labor Film Series 1997 - T-Shirt (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Rochester Labor Film Series 1994 - T-Shirt (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Magnet - 1888 One Hundred 1988 Years of Solidarity - Rochester & Vicinity Labor Council - AFL-CIO (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Rochester Labor Film Series - 2005 -- T-Shirt (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Rochester Labor Film Series - 2002 -- T-Shirt (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Rochester Labor Film Series - 2003 -- T-Shirt (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Rochester Labor Film Series - 1995 -- T-Shirt (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Rochester Labor Film Series - 12th Annual -- T-Shirt (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Rochester Labor Film Series - Best of the Fest -- T-Shirt (Box 4, Folder 7)
- NYSUT Local 2842, Faculty Association, Monroe Community College -- T-Shirt (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Broadsides - advertising different Labor Day Parades, 1986-1989 (Box 5, Folder 1)